There's a new kid on the block.
Home Alone 3 is a comedy, family film directed by Raja Gosnell.
9-year-old Alex Pruitt is home alone with the chicken pox.
Turns out, due to a mix-up among nefarious spies, Alex was
given a toy car concealing a top-secret microchip.
Now Alex must fend off the spies as they try to
break into his house to get it back.
Alex Pruitt, played by Alex D. Linz.
Peter Beaupre, played by Olek Krupa.
Alice Ribbons, played by Rya Kihlstedt.
Burton Jernigan, played by Lenny Von Dohlen.
Earl Unger, played by David Thornton.
Karen Pruitt, played by Haviland Morris.
Home Alone 3 is a 1997 American crime comedy film, directed
by Raja Gosnell, and written by John Hughes.
It is the third in the Home Alone film series and stars Alex D.
Linz and Haviland Morris.
The plot follows Alex Pruitt, an 8-year-old boy who defends his home from a dangerous
group of international criminals working for a terrorist organization.
Home Alone 3 was released on December 12, 1997, by 20th Century Fox.
The film grossed $79 million and received negative reviews from critics.
It was followed by a made-for-television sequel, Home Alone 4, in 2002.
The film explores themes of winter, burglar, bravery,
computer chip, family relationships.
The tone is lighthearted.